chto_eto_bylo: HeyGuys
ququa111: HeyGuys
DazPlay1337: aye
agesmith52: Shalom
buklao: Oof
blackburn1911: hey
stannerindia: hi geo how are you today ?
DazPlay1337: kick his ass
buklao: Have you tried using reinforcement learning to play chest
aktw_: Olaf
th3_maj0r: yoyo
JSPeterson: where you been bro I'll come back
tomcr00s3: gonna use minimax search!
fn_mad: HEY
tomcr00s3: I only have 34 battery though
un3okapi: someone is speaking weeb in the background
tomcr00s3: hehe
buklao: Is the butterfly keyboard aids?
JSPeterson: do some emus bro PS3 emu
tomcr00s3: love keyboard
tomcr00s3: new map 13" 2018
tomcr00s3: *mbp
Jaany: hey hey boss
buklao: Does that garbage even have a quad core
brandoncode: where are you?
slovn1k: @tomcr00s3 nice
tomcr00s3: in the cloud
tomcr00s3: I am in the cloud
brandoncode: haha
DazPlay1337: geo how was your day?
Jaany: Kreygasm thats fantastic
tomcr00s3: good
tomcr00s3: I walked a lot
Jaany: Hows the weather in the cloud
buklao: Yell penis
tomcr00s3: cloudy
tomcr00s3: always
un3okapi: I've got a rope geo, I'll come visit you in the clouds
Jaany: Nice
Jeppelelle: long time no stream, thought you where dead or on a hooker spree like McAfee
ququa111: more cloud humours
JSPeterson: you work too hard
buklao: Play the penis game
un3okapi: @buklao he's too old for that
DazPlay1337: mature for that*
return100000001: !uptime
keepingtrckofthisacct: @buklao 'ain't nobody got time for that'
keepingtrckofthisacct: @return100000001 5min
un3okapi: https://www.google.co.jp/ ...
un3okapi: is he in japan?
SylensEdits: was you able to do xcode select install on mojave it keeps saying failed @tomcr00s3
un3okapi: We can hear you.
buklao: cheer50 yell penis
yagurastation: is this Asia?
un3okapi: Yeah I think he's in japan
return100000001: @keepingtrckofthisacct ty
SylensEdits: can you tell the trick to install it I cant seem to find it @tomcr00s3
buklao: What vpn do you use
tomcr00s3: how is my new streaming setup btw?
un3okapi: Wonderful
tomcr00s3: sweet
myaocat: hello geohot
tomcr00s3: perhaps sometimes I'll be in places where I can talk
un3okapi: @tomcr00s3 do you know any japanese?
myaocat: we can't hear you
buklao: Just yell penis
yagurastation: Steam is good
agesmith52: Good, but I miss the mechanical keyboard🙄
SylensEdits: :( not going to show can you link it perhaps @tomcr00s3
ddd_dota: @tomcr00s3 are you gonna be doing deepfakes any time soon?
white_male20: forsenDab
buklao: cheer35 PENNNISS
buklao: Pen island.
juniperus1976: are you in a restaurant?
un3okapi: @buklao ???
buklao: Cafe probs
buklao: Hello
buklao: Do you guys like pen island
white_male20: @tomcr00s3 forsenDab dab or prerecorded
DazPlay1337: Sorry for the annoying Twitch chat lol...
buklao: It's not pre recorded..
white_male20: LuL
Mua_987410: in public, no talk
Crying_Potato: PogChamp
Crying_Potato: PogChamp stream
myaocat: what are you coding?
tomcr00s3: so quiet, you like?
DazPlay1337: I enjoy this haha.
SylensEdits: :( not going to show can you link it perhaps @tomcr00s3
ic0mrade: yes is so quiet because we lear from the MASTER @tomcr00s3
DazPlay1337: WE DEED!!! o_O
LuminousCS: can you not charge it where you're at?
buklao: Lol thinner lighter less faster
un3okapi: this is good white noise to facilitate my sleep
LuminousCS: ^
tomcr00s3: I forgot charger at home
buklao: ^
LuminousCS: ah that sucks lol
myaocat: what are you coding?
DazPlay1337: Hack the power outlet. xD
th3_maj0r: good move George
petrexxy: lmao
SonOfSatan: hack yourself a self made charger lol
buklao: Fart on the keyboard I hear that works through thermodynamics
myaocat: try wireless charging might work
memoryleak: code faster 4Head
petrexxy: speed code
newtomcroose: why just 1080 ?
myaocat: why not 4k?
newtomcroose: why not 720 or 480 ?
myaocat: stealing wifi bandwith
SylensEdits: can you show how you install xcode select install @tomcr00s3
buklao: How can he output 4k isn't the screen 2.5k
newtomcroose: ok , i wanna sell my bed and buy a good internet , i be nothing if i sleep on the floor
LuminousCS: wouldnt lower quality give you lower cpu usage thus lower battery consumption?
un3okapi: ask if they have a mbp charger at the cafe desk. :) Say "mac book charger desu ka?"
th3_maj0r: desu ka ahahahah
SonOfSatan: 1 hacker boi vs python chess
newtomcroose: bro , i just wanna dance with somebody
newtomcroose: @tomcr00s3 ok , i wanna sell my bed and buy a good internet , i be nothing if i sleep on the floor
buklao: Ai chess
tomcr00s3: ahh I think it's repeating moves
tomcr00s3: triple repeat = fail
newtomcroose: @tomcr00s3 just sell your bed
th3_maj0r: go there with google translate and ask for a charger. Go George!!
Cs_nothing: where's he streaming from? is he out at some event?
buklao: Cafe
LuminousCS: sounds like japan
newtomcroose: why safari :D ? why not chrome ?
th3_maj0r: yeah, probably japan
buklao: Or he's at one of those message parlers that end with a happy ending
un3okapi: Definitely japan. :/
buklao: Waiting
buklao: For his turn
LuminousCS: wHy NoT cHrOmE
newtomcroose: no probably china , or north korea :|
tomcr00s3: fuck chrome
tomcr00s3: fuck google
LuminousCS: true
buklao: Chrome eats ram
newtomcroose: @tomcr00s3 even facebook ? :))
Cs_nothing: OMEGALUL
tomcr00s3: nah it's the login shit they pulled
buklao: And extensions have monero miners lol
SonOfSatan: lol
petrexxy: googley boogley
newtomcroose: people like instagram
tomcr00s3: google is really a sad story
DazPlay1337: lol
tomcr00s3: I know people who worked there for years
tomcr00s3: and recently quit cause so disillusions
Cs_nothing: anyone know whaf loging shit hes talking about? i haven't been keeping up
un3okapi: is waymo a sad story? ;)
tomcr00s3: lol
keepingtrckofthisacct: @tomcr00s3 those setting can now be changed. opt out
newtomcroose: @tomcr00s3 if u working for facebook or google u could buy a tesla mode 3 . am i loser :| ?
tomcr00s3: we don't talk about self driving cars on twitch chan
buklao: I saw a company using an iPhone and they have level 4 at an event I went to
un3okapi: ok :(
tomcr00s3: SDC = ban
tomcr00s3: only twitchchess
SylensEdits: :(
th3_maj0r: You change browser more frequently than your t-shirt
DazPlay1337: Oh for real?
un3okapi: the recent scopie was boring without you. :(
newtomcroose: only twitchies
myaocat: what is sdc?
un3okapi: sorry last 1
un3okapi: I'm done
acheesedanish00: twitchchess > SDC
SonOfSatan: Google now logs you into the gmail, or the browser and other services if you login into just one of their services
newtomcroose: what u eat ?
newtomcroose: @tomcr00s3 what u eating ? waffle ? :D
un3okapi: @myaocat self driving car
Cs_nothing: @tomcr00s3 according to you, what is good code, and what is bad code?
newtomcroose: omg this is a caffe strea,
keepingtrckofthisacct: @tomcr00s3 why did you choose minimax for this?
return100000001: those girls make me angry
newtomcroose: @Cs_nothing bad code is bad code , and good code is just geo codes :|
Mua_987410: sounds like japanese
newtomcroose: japanese talking crazy
petrexxy: no charger? thats a checkmate! haha
Cs_nothing: @newtomcroose LUL i really wanna know tho
newtomcroose: @tomcr00s3 this is a plan for next stream :D = https://projecteuler.net/problem=600
acheesedanish00: if you ask what bad code is on twitchchess you probably write bad code
newtomcroose: just linus torvalds write good code :|
juniperus1976: it much less entertaining than with talking
keepingtrckofthisacct: 16% left!
Crying_Potato: I have no clue what is happening
newtomcroose: When I find myself in times of trouble, Mother Mary comes to me Speaking words of wisdom, let it be And in my hour of darkness she is standing right in front of me Speaking words of wisdom, let it be Let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be Whisper words of wisdom, let it be
DazPlay1337: Turn brightness down. :P
keepingtrckofthisacct: won't help. the streaming is killing it.
DazPlay1337: @Crying_Potato He is scripting a chess bot.
Kobayawaka: aurHype aurHype aurHype aurHype aurHype
SonOfSatan: greekShhh
keepingtrckofthisacct: 12%
BrainIet: FBtouchdown
theGeekPirate: I'd still lose to it FeelsBadMan
un3okapi: that opening is not canon
return100000001: i have drop, u have guys ?
RuhAdamTR: PogChamp
jurodiwy_777: PogChamp
Roundlay: Are you in Japan?
BrainIet: the japanese grills in the background TPFufun TPFufun
un3okapi: Whoahdude good trade
SonOfSatan: @Roundlay japan came to steal his chess bot
Roundlay: God they love talking about their gohan
un3okapi: LUL
return100000001: lol
Roundlay: roundl2
keepingtrckofthisacct: chess whuppin'
SonOfSatan: Watching this makes me want to write a chess bot myself, but first I need to learn actual chess greekWeird
Roundlay: @SonOfSatan same lol
return100000001: he is loosing against his own chess ai lol
shevchenkounchainged: chess bot is done
un3okapi: @tomcr00s3 FailFish
SonOfSatan: 2 minutes later: "Elon was right, we need to regulate AI" greekYikes
BrainIet: ^ LUL
newtomcroose: dont trust everything george say . :|
Roundlay: @tomcr00s3 Have you read Crystal Society by any chance?
DazPlay1337: It knows haha
th3_maj0r: ahahah
RuhAdamTR: lol
tomcr00s3: draw?
Roundlay: rip
tomcr00s3: omg I'm pathethic
un3okapi: yeah
un3okapi: draw
newtomcroose: @tomcr00s3 who say the toys are funny ?
th3_maj0r: 7%
Kobayawaka: it was just a warmup
tomcr00s3: battery dying
un3okapi: It's ok. Just create a bot that codes better than you.
newtomcroose: @tomcr00s3 media is scam . dont do media
tomcr00s3: we'll be streaming more
tomcr00s3: plz siub
tomcr00s3: *sub
un3okapi: later tonight?
DazPlay1337: Cya geo nice seeing you.
tomcr00s3: I need money
SylensEdits: :(
newtomcroose: @tomcr00s3 for rice ?
un3okapi: you're rich.
tomcr00s3: love ❤️ 💕 💗 💖
tomcr00s3: I want ramen!
newtomcroose: @tomcr00s3 for rice ? u need money
th3_maj0r: Wtf u are rich george
tomcr00s3: not just rice!
tomcr00s3: move up in the world
newtomcroose: @tomcr00s3 maybe a girl ?
tomcr00s3: nah, overpriced
newtomcroose: @tomcr00s3 world is scam :|
tomcr00s3: ramen is a good deal
tomcr00s3: not here
newtomcroose: @tomcr00s3 bro . world is a fake news
tomcr00s3: in cloud, all is wonderful
stoogethomas: hack my bank account you can pay your own subs with my bank
tomcr00s3: and I am happy
un3okapi: ramen in the cloud
tomcr00s3: byebye 5%
Roundlay: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LhJ7R2asi0Y
th3_maj0r: byeee
newtomcroose: @tomcr00s3 checkout https://projecteuler.net/problem=600 for next
Jeppelelle: he dead
newtomcroose: GOOD BY MY MOTHERRRRRR
Jaany: baai